Welcome to the future. It's a no-brainer.
Harrison Bergeron is a science fiction, tv movie film directed by Bruce Pittman.
"All men are not created equal.
It is the purpose of the Government to make them so." This is the premise of the Showtime
film adaption of Kurt Vonnegut's futuristic short story Harrison Bergeron.
The film centers around a young man (Harrison) who is smarter than his peers, and is not affected by the
usual "Handicapping" which is used to train all Americans so everyone is of equal intelligence.
Harrison Bergeron, played by Sean Astin.
Phillipa, played by Miranda de Pencier.
President McCloskey, played by Eugene Levy.
Charlie, played by Howie Mandel.
Diana Moon Glampers, played by Andrea Martin.
John Klaxon, played by Christopher Plummer.
Harrison Bergeron is a science fiction television movie film loosely adapted
from Kurt Vonnegut's 1961 dystopian  short story of the same name.
It was produced for Showtime and first screened on August 13, 1995.
It was released to VHS in 1998.
The tone is thought_provoking.